To slice the kohlrabi, first we are going to cut off these extra bits here and make it as smooth as possible.
And the you will want to cut a flat side so you won't have it rolling around when you are slicing.
You want to cut down a nice flat side like that.
And then with a large sharp French knife, French chef knife, you are going to slice off a bit there.
Then go about a millimeter, two millimeters and slice really thin slices.
You want to keep you knife moving in a nice downward motion.
Kind of moving the knife like this at the same time.
If you slice one in half like that, don't worry.
Maybe you could use it still.
And you want to slice it as thinly as possible.
So you have a petal that is flexible.
You don't want it to be stiff like this is the end but that is much too stiff.
You want it to be flexible like that.
And you slice the whole vegetable all the way down.
If you get, if you make some mistakes, like you cut a piece off and you get a lump there, you can cut a thicker piece to get flat again and then continue on.